[Prasha]
First of all, click on the login ID,
login by entering the ID and password and
click on motor insurance. As soon as we
click on motor insurance, the
screen is
asking for our registration number. Before entering the registration number,
an arrow is showing on the left side,
we will click on that arrow. As soon as we click on the arrow, the
package OTP option of all the vehicles is being shown to us, four
wheeler, two wheeler, bus, PCV, so right now we are
making two wheeler third party insurance,
so we will click on two wheeler third party.
As soon as we click on two wheeler third
party, the
registration number is now being shown on our screen.
We have to fill the registration number,
we have to fill the details. So now I will
enter the registration number of my vehicle.
As soon as I fill the registration number,
an option will come up, Fetch Vehicle Details, then
click on this option. As soon as
you click on this option, the automatic portal will
automatically fetch all the details of your vehicle,
which is manufacture, model,
registration, registration year,
manufacturing  It will fetch all the details of this vehicle.
See, the city is Haryana Bhiwani.
Registration and then the manufacturer which is
Activa 3G Honda Motorcycle,
all the details have been fetched automatically.
First registration
date, year of manufacture, customer status,
policy start
date, current registration type is individual. If the
customer's name is corporate or
partnership, then we will select that.
If it does not pick up these details, then we
can manually fill in these details. This
means we have to make insurance for one year,
2 years or 3 years.
All the details have been checked. If the details are
okay, then we will click on the recalculate option.
As soon as we click on recalculate,
it is showing the premium of Rs.
14162, but now we have to make third
party insurance of minimum amount. So we will
click on click here, then we will
add customized covers and remove them. We will click on the cover which does not have
a valid driving license and then
recalculate as soon as  We will
recalculate the premium and it will change.
See this
is an insurance of 843 714 plus inclusive
GST. By adding GST, the
third party insurance of your two wheeler will
become
843. Then click on submit. You
can also check the details by doing view premium breakup.
See this, insurance of 714 has been made.
This is the insurance of minimum amount
plus GST has been added. 9 The total premium will
become
8843. You can check all the details by clicking on view premium breakup.
Making third party insurance is very
easy. So see, engine number, chassis number,
details have been fetched automatically. If it is
not fetched, then you can fill it manually.
But cross check the details fetched by the portal, if there is any
mistake, then
our option comes for KYC no.
of customer, corporate, complete
KYC or we can skip it also.
Now we will complete it and add the PAN number.
We have three options, RPAN number,
Aadhaar number and NAN.  Otherwise, we can do KYC
through whichever option we want to do it.
We will
enter the PAN number and DB.
As soon as we enter the DB, an
option of submit will appear in front of us. If
we click on the submit option, the portal will
fetch all these details, address and email ID number.
You cannot change the owner name.
You can also change the address.
See, the full name on this account has been
fetched by the portal. Then click on proceed. As soon as we
proceed, this owner name which is the
insured name has been frozen.
We can also change the address. Mobile number,
I will enter any random mobile number now
and the email ID has been fetched in it.
If you want to change it, you can also change it. You can add the
pin code, city, district, state,
whatever you want according to yourself. You
can add it. Then the option of add GST is coming. If you want to
add GST or nominee details
or if you do
not want to add previous policy details, then
click on create proposal.
Send Payment Link If you want to change your mail ID number
then change it and click on
submit. This is your third part insurance.